Setumadhava Giridhar Kathawate

206-739-4983 setugk@uw.edu <u>www.setumadhava.com</u>

About

Passionate designer having 2.8 years of experience seeking opportunities to solve complex user & business problems through elegant, research informed product & experience designs. Other interests include Machine Learning & Behavioral Psychology.

Skills

Interaction Design & Prototyping, Axure, Framer, Invision, Interface & Visual design, Wireframes, Sketch, Photoshop, Illustrator, Solid understanding of Research methodologies to analyze & measure user behavior, Contextual Inquiry, User Interviews, Personas, Designing usable patterns & products, HTML/CSS/SASS, Python, Arduino, Cross Functional Collaboration skills, Design strategy, Agile methodologies, Machine Learning basics, Android (Material) & iOS design languages.

Relevant Courses

User-Centered Design, Usability Studies, Data Science for UX Researchers, Visual Communication, Interaction Design & Prototyping, Machine Learning (Coursera).

Experience

PREMERA BLUE CROSS, UX DESIGNER

MAY 2017 - PRESENT

Leading the UX efforts to design Premera's healthcare search experience to help customers confidently find the right healthcare they're looking for. After shipping the search tool, customer satisfaction score went up from the low 2s to mid 4s (on a scale of 1-5).

EVENTOSAUR, CO-FOUNDER, PRODUCT DESIGNER

MAR 2015 - JAN 2017

Designed an e-commerce platform to help people plan their traditional Indian events easily by connecting hosts with event service vendors. Led the design & research teams and handled end-to-end product design process to design the web app.

UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON LIBRARIES, USABILITY RESEARCHER

SEP 2016 - MAR 2017

Conducted usability study on the UW Library search website with 12 participants. Identified usability concerns & proposed opportunities for improvement through study data analysis.

EXPEDIA INC, INTERACTION DESIGN INTERN

JUN 2016 - SEP 2016

Designed a concept mobile web interface to improve Expedia's hotel shopping experience by simplifying the room browsing and checkout process and also by providing customers more control over their beds & occupancy preferences.

Education

M.S IN HUMAN CENTERED DESIGN & ENGINEERING

SEP 2015 - MAR 2017

University of Washington, Seattle; GPA 3.92/4.0

BACHELOR'S IN ELECTRONICS & COMMUNICATIONS ENGINEERING

AUG 2006 - JUN 2010

Visvesvaraya Technological University, Bangalore, India; GPA 6.9/10.0

Awards

BEST GRADUATE CAPSTONE PROJECT - PUMP IT UP

JUN 2017

University of Washington, Seattle

Proposed an efficient way to manage water in Indian homes by designing an Android app and a concept IOT system that provides residents better control & information about their water use thereby reducing water waste.